i'm going to speak jakarta and the other one to
我要讲雅加达和另一个
the rib inside all mourning be this
所有哀悼中的肋骨是这个
challenge for me to speak after all
挑战让我说话
all night people she offers to do it
她提供的通宵达旦的服务
in following manner from and user
来自用户的以下方式
perspective so what do to emines b you
观点，那么怎样做才能使你
use up respective of jamaica system is
用尽牙买加系统是
my door vlaanderen open source like a
我的门vlaanderen开源像
it is individual contributors evangelist
它是个人贡献者的传播者
organization most of them have widely
他们大多数都有广泛的组织
communiqué and contextual idylle
公报和语境
greece and chinese series no20 another
希腊和中国20世纪系列另一个
actor life at news of the technology
科技新闻中的演员生活
in the guys who does your life project
在做你的人生计划的家伙中
and deliver business value and
并提供业务价值和
technology in gaye thin mesh
盖网薄网格技术
lost because jabbari this symbol of
失去了，因为贾巴里这个象征
technical stability and going my joy
技术的稳定性，让我开心
transformation even in the sign for java
即使在Java标志中也可以进行转换
ee 6 france with so to behave between
ee 6 France与
naive optimizes are exaggerated
天真的优化被夸大了
pc we are six battles
个人电脑，我们是六场战斗
propose to speak about
建议谈论
fiorenzo good me mayamba ziclean java
fiorenzo好我mayamba ziclean java
user group say and hold java user
用户组说并按住Java用户
spain mandeure linden indie haiti
西班牙mandeure林登独立海地
smoothly them with jabba highway iv
与贾巴高速公路四顺利
online anathos group company we build
我们建立的在线anathos集团公司
and digital platforms on behalf of
和数字平台代表
our business initial business area
我们的业务初始业务领域
domanys payments and we have expanded gold
多付款，我们扩大了黄金
capacity to process secure electronic
处理安全电子的能力
transaction three areas that jazze
交易三个领域的爵士乐
e-government health food gate
电子政务健康食品大门
the seizures hadj ndao my knock
癫痫发作hajjdao我的敲门声
wilfert start with shorts
wilfert从短裤开始
retrospective loring of past is
过去的追溯性租金是
essential to look into the wild
野外必不可少的
the time that has led to close native
导致关闭本地人的时间
application will speakman specifies curie
申请者将指定发言人居里
abbott java there to wil explain why why
那里的abbott java将解释为什么
i'm willing to be in belgium
我愿意在比利时
users and last but not least we
用户，最后但并非最不重要的一点
succeeds in fearing future shocks
成功地担心未来的冲击
world time they do so this is a
他们这样做的世界时间
personal representation deliberately
故意代表个人
simplified of the evolution of the java
简化了Java的发展
platform from the issue is it where
问题的平台是哪里
work his coming
工作他的到来
first world gets you it's what the funk
第一世界让你，这就是放克
kool the prehistoric times because the
因为史前时代
specifications were made in 'top down'
规格为“自上而下”
approach with up consider in the
在考虑的方法
developer experience index lei all
开发人员体验指数全部
extra complexity
额外的复杂性
a strong size rajohnson road book
强大的拉约翰森路线图
very interesting proposing pragmatic
非常有趣的提议
are closer to it all develop
更接近一切
facebook applications to deuce a
Facebook应用程序推演
mourning or impact in java community
在Java社区中的哀悼或影响
is beginning of the spring framework it
是Spring框架的开始
also had direct impact on the
也对
jabbari platform for the first time with
jabbari平台首次与
a very five
五个
is of development 3 really taken into
是发展3真正纳入
consider nice
认为不错
jp instead of the dead mad the cndb
jp而不是疯了的cndb
annotations
注解
at 9 am to 9 am but john marston
在上午9点至上午9点，但约翰·马斯顿
oise and yves de weezer jobs at the peaks
Oise和Yves de Weezer在高峰时期的工作
framework develops beginning king beef
框架开发开始王牛肉
in hibernate daub which by the way to
在休眠涂抹中
sidiailles context in dependence and
sidiailles依存关系和
inception sauce cydia has become
初始酱cydia已成为
foundation of the way
方式的基础
used by 6-1 and taxes to zouglou between
由6-1使用并向zouglou征税
the different specifications
不同规格
external technologies
外部技术
jamai seven oise essentially
贾迈七瓦兹本质上
continuation or additional fischer
延续或额外的菲舍尔
jazze batch processing jason processing
jazze批处理jason处理
websocket
的WebSocket
aurora jabbari was good bad and the good
奥罗拉·贾巴里（Aurora jabbari）很好，也很好
friday of between innovation and
创新与创新之间的星期五
standardization
标准化
it is to be the place to standard
这是成为标准的地方
innovations which was right by the way
顺带一提的创新
for now jp it goes down curie
现在，jp它下降了居里
standardization hibernate spring
标准化冬眠弹簧
batchali in french touch an as we have
法国的batchali触摸我们
said jboss team a space the way to
说jboss团队空间通往
there is a particle hours the day before i was
我去的前一天有一个粒子小时
in christine your taste of fit long
在克里斯汀，你很健康
term this project i see you came in
这个项目，我看到你进来了
payment
付款
the paint domain we need backward
我们需要向后绘画的领域
technical compatibility capitalization
技术兼容性大写
on the technology and also be series
在技​​术上，也是系列
complete ci
完整词
an authorized audit
授权审核
somain bidja i was not innovating
somain bidja我不是在创新
at least it was taken as from good fit for
至少它被认为是非常适合
some of project
一些项目
after jah is even
在扎哈甚至
the price of change
改变的代价
this article he is developing this calling for
他正在撰写这篇文章，呼吁
better cooperation between them up with
他们之间更好的合作
good practices this hunt continues
狩猎的良好做法仍在​​继续
diploma
文凭
you have to structure this code
您必须构建此代码
noci couet lannes polyglot persistent
Noci couet lannes多语种持久
if a solution that jazze mongodb in
如果解决方案在爵士mongodb
straight straight challenging traditional 6
直直挑战传统6
kw data base macro service exemplify by
kw数据库宏服务示例如下
netflix
Netflix公司
hand pretty shapes to live by those
手工制作漂亮的形状
factors for heroes kick except that
英雄踢的因素，除了
cantonal smooth revolution of kurt
库特州的平稳革命
cobain and s
cobain和s
a word felt reactive programming it
一个词感到反应性编程
order to get better stability and
为了获得更好的稳定性和
scalability
可扩展性
he of plants
他的植物
so in a few years
所以几年
a new models of development immerge
沉浸式发展的新模式
what we know gold crown and yves
我们所知道的金王冠和伊夫
typical applications in the image of a
图像中的典型应用
dirty man francs bowls service call
脏人法郎碗服务电话
it my too served six years note
我也服了六年笔记
yes this polyglot assistant 6-1 biltine
是的，这多语言助手6-1胆汁
monitoring resiliency el sheikh
监控弹性谢赫
but kingdom hearts of develop this good
但是王国的内心发展这种美好
practices and the club france
惯例和俱乐部法国
so by twenty fifteen we can say that the
所以到二十十五点我们可以说
gap between market expectations pronesti
市场预期之间的差距pronesti
of applications javari adwise in
javari adwise中的应用程序
so what happened to work is eight in
所以发生的事情是八分之一
tahiti fortune between anti sixtine
塔希提岛反六丁星之间的命运
basic lee ann prunty
基本的李安修剪
fifteen are basic nothing
十五岁基本没什么
since he is farid seriously inpi six tin
由于他是一个愚蠢的人，严重地印了六锡
whistle initiative has native code
举报倡议拥有本机代码
work oit john roos and ap by the woman
女人工作约翰·罗斯和ap
in order to restore specifications
为了恢复规格
lookalike by winning petition over 20 miles
通过赢得20英里的请愿书看起来很像
trying to win phone tracker
试图赢得手机追踪器
harmos at the same time the mic
同时吹奏麦克风
low-profile project start it boy blue
低调的项目启动它男孩蓝色
boys band of all of them will accept body
他们所有人的男孩乐队都会接受身体
in order to define and open
为了定义和打开
specification loud claude native jackson
规格响亮的克劳德·本·杰克逊
and yves applications java one in october
和yves应用Java十月之一
to rome to the connections shared news north
到罗马与北方的联系分享新闻
beach road map and objective was to renew
海滩路线图和目标是更新
platforms in two years
两年内的平台
on it's way back on track and community
回到正轨和社区
enthusiastic higuain ipad ipod r robert
热情的伊瓜因人ipad ipod r罗伯特
horry enthusiastic even in world in the
即使在世界上，也能充满热情
side by side hockey and we started
并排曲棍球，我们开始
are you one year after java it was
你是Java之后的一年吗
actually release 8 glassfish fault 2 0
实际释放8条玻璃鱼故障2 0
to sion
走向
with the following mind change alignment
随心所欲的改变
swiss is going to have to remix java ee
瑞士将不得不重新混合Java ee
6 heitz delivered one year after the ice
冰冻一年后交付了6架海兹
man so it was right to take into account
男人，所以考虑到它是正确的
oxo nord stream fart buck rogers new
oxo nord流放屁buck rogers新
times and countries hansson http everything supports
时代与国家汉森http一切支持
with sand is strong level
用沙子是很强的水平
hassine craignos evans but if there is
hassine craignos埃文斯，但如果有
other rounds 2 0
其他回合2 0
klein side reactive program inside the
内部的klein侧反应程序
stac service all the canvas
stac服务所有画布
we serve said server side event
我们说服务器端事件
jason processing and in france
杰森·加工和法国
jason patch and panthers new
杰森·帕特和黑豹新
specifications jason btu bind java
规范jason btu绑定java
classes '' and then structure à de new
类”，然后构造àde new
security specifications bringing
安全规范带来
simplification computerization
简化计算机化
his overlord taste to continue shon bat
他的霸主味继续蝙蝠侠
nothing revolution by the way it is one
顺便说一句，没有什么革命
man show ning go ahead old java dotnet sa
男子秀宁继续旧的Java dotnet sa
it has been commissions for the
它一直是佣金
benefit of peter forster must modern
彼得·福斯特的好处必须现代
its after 30 years of relative stability
经过30年的相对稳定性
in summer twenty seventeen winter's bone
在夏天二十七冬天的骨头
in for this with everything shanxi
一切都在山西
faust mido cust oracle announcement
浮士德Mido Cust Oracle公告
it's time to stop the development of
是时候停止发展了
jah bailly
贾拜伊
mid september watson foundations for
九月中旬的沃森基金会
this future at java platforms ee 6 nine
在Java平台EE 6上的这个未来
inch allah i hate world delivered at 2.5
我讨厌世界的英寸阿拉在2.5
kind of being disrupted glassware broadcast
某种被干扰的玻璃器皿广播
in september the top level iphone
九月顶级iPhone
say here zlotoff change shorts
在这里说zlotoff换短裤
montaufray soa the use of the technology
montaufray soa使用该技术
and rise many concerns 1.18 difficulty
并引起许多关注1.18难度
web
卷筒纸
perspective stone of fresh breath
清新口气的透视石
omnium she offers richard with you
她向你提供理查德的奥姆尼姆
some questions are expectations as
一些问题是期望
having mind concerns oise
头脑担忧
between success both disciplines for
在两个学科的成功之间
me
我
until standards dissipate on the ground
直到标准消散
authority and bob dylan
权威与鲍勃·迪伦
ja poor's standard hobby's
杰·穷的标准爱好
djawad technologies
djawad技术
so when the decision was taken by
所以当决定由
racole myphone station was what will
racole myphone站是什么
make and open specification
制作和打开规格
under the auspices havana open source
在哈瓦那主持下开源
dead foundation valley bolzano
死基谷博尔扎诺
owner make me I would bet
老板让我敢打赌
françoise and jessy pi
法兰西和杰西·皮
there is no i 10 below right
右下方没有我10
yonne batziens drops 12:14 strength
约讷·巴齐恩斯（Yonne Batziens）下降12:14力量
one
一
he eclipses myth michael profile project
他使神话迈克尔的个人资料项目黯然失色
which was clearly
显然
open specification cannois zai started
开放规范cannois zai开始
modest glassware lies in summer 36
适度的玻璃器皿在于夏天36
sixtine
sixtine
we the best and sweet java specification
我们最好，最甜蜜的Java规范
jax rs 6 10 to 1 18
jax rs 6 10至1 18
alma stage myth l bird bits this little
阿尔玛·舞台神话l鸟咬了一下
hold the time
把握时间
successor libor for release and five a
释放的后继解放者和五个
presentation in hope you man so this is
演示文稿，希望您能，所以这是
very very positive it indications
非常非常积极的迹象
groups sellers to competitors
将卖方分组为竞争对手
av john terry is strong all told fan and
约翰·特里（AV john Terry）坚强地告诉粉丝
open specification this is a good sign
开放规范，这是一个好兆头
for jakarta and the future of the bay
雅加达和海湾的未来
this 50 50 positive reason indicators there
这50 50个积极的原因指标
eclipse foundation and itself in fact it
蚀基础及其本身
cost input will be the focus home sellers
成本投入将成为房屋卖家关注的焦点
neutrality forlin stand am at the museum j
中立福林站在博物馆j
6 ft lp intellectual property
LP 6 ft知识产权
specifications wazi ownership to
规范wazi所有权
leading specifications
领先规格
yes jakarta i
是的，雅加达我
watania wanders elbow and specifications
瓦塔尼亚徘徊的肘部和规格
louis drones to this open source standard
路易斯无人机遵循此开源标准
project ensuring no single chip music
确保没有单芯片音乐的项目
by another very interesting indicators
通过另一个非常有趣的指标
tell the fans the company is weak tonight
告诉球迷今晚公司表现不佳
totally external all
全部外部
giovanni ecosystems sofa
乔瓦尼生态系统沙发
mycroft have you got they said it to
mycroft你明白了吗
john the project has been for you
约翰，这个项目适合你
you going my company said opportunity
你去我公司说机会
or threat happiness victor clan founder of
或威胁幸福胜利者氏族创始人
the Thai company 100 at times in order
泰国公司100有时
to see how to look jamai a haka scala a
看看外观jamai a haka scala a
joke time it was it was in total our
开玩笑的时间，这是我们总的
Gaulish autonomous zone
戈里什自治区
in total ten matches and decided to stop
在总共十场比赛中决定停止
tuo positive that's why i'm very happy
o积极，这就是为什么我很高兴
to see a live band on the run
去看现场乐队
we offer yves sinot james
我们提供伊夫·西诺特·詹姆斯
useful and positive find another positive 5
有用和积极的发现另一个积极的5
he is vital
他很重要
and as all answer yes to get up and
所有人都回答是就站起来
open specification in agree on
公开规范
combines legitimate here ausy eclipse one is
结合这里合法的日食之一是
young
年轻
my 70 concerts nor good governance
我的70场音乐会也不善良
of the ring twenty years dissiper is
环二十年的消耗是
to honor jobs the guardian governance
尊重监护人的工作
etc specifications noise manager sister to
等规格噪音经理妹妹
bastille specification requests young
巴斯蒂勒规格要求年轻
expert boobs airways client delivered
专家胸部航空公司客户交付
bowl scientific documentation m
碗科学文献记录仪
howell define lifecycle that promises to
豪威尔定义了有望实现的生命周期
jisr feminization to find and release
jisr女性化找到并释放
and the overall coordination birds
和整体协调鸟
breeders so this model has enabled
饲养员，因此该模型已启用
platforms to last ranker beat it has
最后排名击败的平台
not been and bolt or 1080p rescue coop
没来过和螺栓或1080p救援小屋
on at wind at work with eclipse
在上班日食
foundation
基金会
each specific iphone
每个特定的iPhone
a supplementation reform will be done
将会进行补充改革
and individual open source
和个人开源
the delivery boy who will be the same
送货员将是相同的
compatibility documentation that
兼容性文档
ten offerings coordination will be done
将完成十项产品协调
by the top level and there will be no
到最高层，就不会有
brainer
闻风而动
this jakarta and working in charge of ron
这个雅加达，负责罗恩
management
管理
kosa i think it's important to watch
我觉得重要的是，
djabali has offered that connects from light
djabali提供了从光连接
brand management offensive jalton y a
品牌管理攻势雅尔顿
summed up all day jay z cinterion boat
总结了整天杰伊z inter船
which attaches to wailly to the notes
随便附在笔记上
clearly identified
明确确定
it has no logo no stone marketing
它没有徽标没有石头营销
india a portal north it is defined his
印度北部的门户，它被定义为
style and going process steeman to
风格和流程管理者
again a bingguo man said will be
再次有个冰果男人说
decisive in this sense
在这个意义上是决定性的
my soul to death
我的灵魂要死
having club studies platform as byatt
具有byatt的俱乐部学习平台
mansion giovani it is not the state of
豪宅乔瓦尼这不是状态
thee in bulgaria regarding claudication
您在保加利亚关于c行
fortune writing michael profile to those of
迈克尔将个人资料写成
many jobs
很多工作
this word of mind craftsman with spain
这道心思与西班牙的工匠
this word while sting
刺时这个词
and the daily burn mini port swan
和每天燃烧的迷你港口天鹅
of free yesterday the edition counts years
昨天的免费版本拥有多年的历史
almost all things done for clooney and
几乎所有为克隆而做的事情
chairs are distributed as title houacine
椅子被分配作为标题houacine
security spread like a bridge that
安全就像桥梁一样蔓延开来
heals shon strong tolerance story
治愈小强的容忍故事
10/06 clery hanjin uninhabitable rice haha
10/06 Clery hanjin不可居住的稻哈哈
jakarta folate in haiti how can this
在海地雅加达叶酸怎么会这样
happened
发生
regarding jakarta deny world map save
关于雅加达否认世界地图保存
lisa expected expedition in opposition
丽莎预期反对派
glassfish phaidon wave of all senses
感官的玻璃鱼凤凰波
Jakarta has certified
雅加达已通过认证
nobody
人
my ride no
我的车不行
come from my way from what a wonderful
来自我的方式是多么美好
daspich almost beat will be working
daspich差点拍就可以了
jabite certified eyed peas plug phaidon
Jabite认证的眼豌豆塞
all will be jakarta certif at 6.6 or
所有人都将获得6.6的雅加达认证或
hockey
曲棍球
that mean that glassfish all wilma
那意味着玻璃鱼全是威尔玛
readiness of the new specifications
准备好新规范
process in parallel maicon profile as
在并行maicon配置文件中处理为
planned to get the release the coming
计划在未来发布
soon hwi work
很快工作
jabite same planes
贾比特相同的飞机
so many young at the losers my bitch but
输家中有那么多年轻人
made in that
在那个
profile 3-0 crowd burst of brilliance
简介3-0人群的光彩
claude mailly the aer object platform
claude mailly aer对象平台
apple and inaction
苹果与无为
time respects the lot regarding any
时间尊重很多关于任何
man was about modularity jabbari we note
男人是关于模块化jabbari的，我们注意到
a good reputation in terms of
良好的声誉
modularity
模块化
the different levels modularity in
不同级别的模块化
modulating health in that specifications
在该规范中调节健康
we need loosli world and highly
我们需要loosli世界和高度
consisting specifications composes
组成规格组成
ballads where he drops our common
他放下我们共同的民谣
cydia foundation and more how
cydia基金会以及更多
configure chan mechanism
配置chan机制
then we need modular to pia is a
那么我们需要模块化的pia是一个
planting wever we like it
我们喜欢种植
sound sonatine jabba module system a
声纳贾巴模块系统
hot you seen as seen as
热你被视为
to from first ep to woody 25 eur john states
从第一季到伍迪25约翰内斯堡国家
would be to define
将是定义
fine all modules name of jakarta hi hi
罚款所有模块的名称雅加达嗨嗨
hi hi
嗨嗨
it's important to all said find them
所有人都说找到他们很重要
as soon as possible because he was held
尽快因为他被关押
by public nor nominal rapetou bantzenheim
通过公众或名义上的拉佩图·班岑海姆
this is technical technical it easy or
这是技术性的技术，这很容易，或者
just have to define and automatic
只需定义并自动
he on board did not say if it did not exist
他在船上没有说是否不存在
of 57 me more difficult because it well
57岁的我比较困难，因为它很好
right to define explicit models
定义明确模型的权利
we propose module a false start a
我们建议模块一个错误的开始
dependence is expected thompson package
预期的汤普森包依赖
so i'll get that this will happen in the
所以我会知道这将发生在
middle of next year iy626 is my
明年中旬，iy626是我的
expectations and we also need modules in
期望，我们还需要以下模块
application server cairn india still in
应用服务器cairn印度仍在
after time is then you love me do not
之后的时间就是你爱我不要
want huddled in eighteen applications
想要缩在十八个应用程序中
servers
服务器
in that matters and bms john hayes budo
在那很重要，并且bms约翰·海耶斯·布多
found in i wanna be seen by sleep spurs
发现在我想被睡眠马刺看到
fast internationals
快速国际
open liberty iso totally different beast
开放自由iso完全不同的野兽
in fact
其实
the server iis folly contribute to
服务器是愚蠢的
to build a guibole of define the
建立一个定义
fisher unit can be my pop have failed
渔民单位可能是我的失败者
we tan figure in standing a couch
我们站在沙发上晒黑了身材
better deals with liberty
更好地处理自由
which in the deep and andy priaulx
在深和安迪priaulx
the Chinese adobe reader app
中国的Adobe Reader应用程序
gold face to face with this one of diplomas
与其中一份文凭面对面
of the six young bitch is being so
六个年轻的母狗是如此
inaugurated date tome i try buy arabic gives
我尝试购买阿拉伯文的就职日期
an excellent job in motorization our
机动化方面的出色工作
applications serve to fine size
应用适合大小
ghadi example prologue albeniz
加迪语范例序言albeniz
iconic
象征
from 6 to 11 years old works in villemagne is
6至11岁在维尔马涅的作品是
willing to the new java here hope
愿意在这里新java
to maynor sion to the connections to be decided
可能决定要确定的连接
of total total and street of the site the risk
站点总数和街道风险
adamson java ee 6 platforms with two
adamson java ee 6平台有两个
fischer release are you
菲舍尔释放你吗
September 910 the cistern abbey
910年9月水箱修道院
and one and death with every year
和每年的死亡
first one next
第一个下一个
based java ee 6 eleven in september
基于Java EE 6的11月11日
in fact sheet charlize heard everything
实际上，查理兹·床单听到了一切
bling production-based innovations
基于生产的创新
of greenhouses rice supports whitby
大米支持惠特比
limited to six months with love at the
限于六个月之久
sedan notes very good conditions
轿车的状况非常好
in long-term contrast supports
长期对比支持
will bring stability a bat production
将为蝙蝠生产带来稳定
will require commercial supports donnart
将需要商业支持
the time of long-term fluid yabassi
长期积液的时间
106,6 at the challenge poor's java ecosystem
106,6挑战穷人的Java生态系统
and the rule in particles shaped like that
规则像这样的粒子
cartonne
cartonne
so what my life young
那我年轻的时候
he has you a fashion cruze on jakarta
他让你在雅加达流行时尚
Iberian challenger fashion bettors
伊比利亚挑战者时尚投注者
belgian in a tube help us with
比利时人在管中帮助我们
benefits
好处
e
Ë
because we think that jazz kantari
因为我们认为爵士坎塔里
esport production
电子竞技生产
perny according to him she has project x
根据他的佩妮，她有专案x
production unit of support
支持生产单位
and i think we do not miss the very
我想我们不要错过
light of innovation hadj abass to sign
创新之光哈迪·阿巴斯签署
this is this is my
这是我的
zero plenty in the world challenge there is a
零世界挑战中有一个
identity of noailles fault discussed
讨论了Noailles断层的身份
the community day follows
社区日如下
there discussions of bonn need for new
有关于波恩需要新的讨论
profile for now finally highlights the
现在的个人资料终于突出了
container awareness many many things of
容器意识的许多事情
ruins in blistering at a service buzz
在服务嗡嗡声中起泡的废墟
wick
演练
my people print kind of
我的人民打印一种
death by many a great challenge
死因众多挑战
all this jabba i is high tech marasmus
这所有的贾巴我都是高科技马拉斯莫斯
dead by this is not a promising follow
死于此不是一个有希望的跟随
up jakarta
雅加达
twenty years our flight open specification
我们的飞行开放规范已有二十年了
100 to day remake
100天重制
a wrong note totaled poesy three
错误的音符合计为诗词三
companies if albi was the ownership of
公司，如果albi是
the leading specifications
领先的规格
[Music]
[音乐]
ten teams foundation in the place to
十支球队的基础
be to make that reminder
是为了提醒
to be honest said no said no then
老实说不
these teams are already available
这些团队已经可用
jakarta
雅加达
michael profile at speed the run fat mike
迈克尔·配置文件的速度运行胖麦克
have profaned space the way into one heart
亵渎了空间进入一颗心
goes by bing mussels fries hours at
去吃贻贝炸薯条数小时
arms in power each country has lessons
每个国家的执政武器都有教训
by bringing olten and yves teachers
通过邀请奥尔滕和伊夫老师
Munich
慕尼黑
his mybet pizza jack a coppice he beats
他打的mybet比萨杰克
the next to you will be decisive
接下来的你将是决定性的
hendaye things that each contribution
每一天的贡献
ivan modest so much difference
伊万谦虚如此多的差异
soan to the use of the technology itunes
渴望使用技术iTunes
visit official jakarta website and
访问雅加达官方网站，并
chips newsletters
芯片通讯
you can follow it in twitter sean avery
您可以在Twitter肖恩·艾弗里（Sean avery）中关注它
can become java guardian sad
可以成为java守护者的伤心人
experience
经验
do you could have said stop loving jah y
你能说停止爱耶吗
have a profile jersey
拥有个人资料
an intrusion failure knowledge tutorials
入侵故障知识教程
and arabic or example this and special there
和阿拉伯语或例子，并在那里特别
had a beat to follow adam been
有节奏跟随亚当
sebastian task north or at an excellent
塞巴斯蒂安任务北部或出色
little shorts that matters and then actor
重要的小短裤，然后是演员
nourishes the flat all is and saint kitts
养育所有的一切和圣基茨
will be important everything is there this fish
这鱼很重要一切都在那里
bagdad wang glassfish size of a
巴格达旺玻璃鱼大小
feed back work and also to feed
反馈工作，也要反馈
convenient
实践
they called me health chen zhu
他们叫我健康陈竺
[Applause]
[鼓掌]